After your first, life is never the same.
After is a romance, drama film directed by Jenny Gage.
Tessa Young is a dedicated student, dutiful daughter and
loyal girlfriend to her high school sweetheart.
Entering her first semester of college, Tessa's guarded world opens up when she meets Hardin Scott, a mysterious and
brooding rebel who makes her question all she thought she knew about herself -- and what she wants out of life.
Tessa Young, played by Josephine Langford.
Hardin Scott, played by Hero Fiennes Tiffin.
Landon Gibson, played by Shane Paul McGhie.
Steph Jones, played by Khadijha Red Thunder.
Noah Porter, played by Dylan Arnold.
Zed Evans, played by Samuel Larsen.
After is a 2019 American romantic drama film directed by Jenny Gage, who co-wrote the screenplay with Susan
McMartin, Tamara Chestna, and Tom Betterton, based on the 2014 novel of the same name by Anna Todd.
It is the first installment in the After film series.
The film stars Hero Fiennes Tiffin and Josephine Langford and follows a young woman who
begins to romance a mysterious student during her first months of college.
The cast includes Selma Blair, Inanna Sarkis, Shane Paul McGhie, Pia Mia, Khadijha Red Thunder,
Dylan Arnold, Samuel Larsen, Jennifer Beals and Peter Gallagher in supporting roles.
After premiered at The Grove in Los Angeles on April 8, 2019, and was
released in the United States on April 12, by Aviron Pictures.
Despite negative reviews from critics, who criticized its screenplay and narrative glamorizing abusive
relationships, it was a commercial success, grossing over $69 million worldwide against its $14 million budget.
A sequel, After We Collided, was released in 2020.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, love,
teenage crush, teenage romance, bad boy.
The tone is emotional.